fadbus.com 2012-02-03

# Privacy Policy - Wholesale Electronics on FadBus.com

**Our company   operation center is in Hong Kong.**

**HongKong Company**  
Company Name:FadBus  Limited  
Company Address:Room 1701(105) 17/F Henan Bldg 90 Faffe Rd Wanchai HK

We put much value on the privacy of our customers and promise to do our best to keep your information safe. Here is the Privacy Policy of FadBus.com, which may explain the following questions.  
1\. What information do we collect from you?  
2\. Why do we collect the information?  
3\. How is your information protected?  
4\. In what form is your information kept?  
5\. Can the account information be corrected or removed?  
6\. How long will we keep the information?  
7\. Notice of changes to this privacy notice.

**1\. What information do we collect from you?**  
**Cookies and Other Computer Information.**  
Cookies are tiny text files stored in your computer when you visit certain web pages that record your preferences. We use cookies to collect aggregate non-personally identifiable information on the visitors to our web site. It often consists of the information of your search preferences, the types of products you have bought, the times you have visited a particular web site, and so on. This type of information is usually associated with a particular computer or IP address, but not with a particular person. You may have to accept cookies to place orders and choose other services on FadBus.com.  
We also contract with third parties to provide us with data collection and reporting services regarding the activities on the site of our customers; meanwhile, also to track and measure the performance of our marketing efforts. These third parties may use cookies and may receive anonymous information about your browsing and buying activity on FadBus.com.  
**Purchase Information**  
FadBus.com accepts your payment through secured third-party payment platforms, such as PayPal and Google Checkout. We will not and cannot get access to your payment information, such as the card number, account number, password, and so on. However, we need to gather the information of your address, name, email address, phone number, postal code, payment method, and so on from these third-party platforms to fulfill your order.  
**Account information**  
You must provide an e-mail address and a password to register on FadBus.com, or you may not be able to access some services.

**2\. Why do we collect the information?**  
We collect the personally identifiable information for the need of providing services, for example, we need the information to fulfill your order; email address and phone number on the other hand are for timely contact in case of anything unusual with your package or latest promotion.  
We collect non-personally identifiable information to offer you better service and to collect marketing information of our website.  
We will not sell or rent the information to any third parties without your express permission or requirement of relevant laws.

**3\. How is your information protected?**  
First of all, we will do our best to secure the website for you to visit and upload information. Meanwhile, we store private information of customers in encrypted form. What’s more, our servers use Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) and encryption technology that works with Netscape Navigator, Microsoft Internet Explorer, Firefox, Safari, and AOL's browser to make sure that your private information won’t be disclosed. Please feel safe to give us your personal information.

**4\. In what form is your information kept?**  
The non-personally identifiable information is stored in your own computer. There will be two cases for personally identifiable information. If you are not a registered member of FadBus.com, your personally identifiable information will be only stored in your order record. That means if you have placed an order on FadBus.com before, we will keep your personally identifiable information ourselves, no matter you are registered or not. If you are a registered member of FadBus.com, your personally identifiable information will not only be stored in your order record, but also be kept as account information in our database.

**5\. Can the account information be corrected or removed?**  
You can correct or remove your account information whenever you like. Just login and then you can change the information or even cancel your account.

**6\. How long will we keep the information?**  
We will keep the information till the regular refreshing of our system and database. Nevertheless, the refresh cycle is quite a long time. We promise to keep your information safe.

**7\. Notice the changes of this privacy policy**.  
This privacy policy was last changed on 12ed August 12, 2010. We reserve the right to change this privacy notice at any time. When it’s changed, we will put a notice on this document to inform everyone. Continuing to use this website means the acceptance of the changes.  
If you have any questions regarding to this policy, please [contact us](http://www.fadbus.com/Help/helpDetail-46.html).
